A makeover project
for your most unhinged leftovers.
The best chefs in Korea will
turn your fridge inside out.
The classy cooking show has returned.
-Chef & My Fridge!
-My Fridge!
LET'S DO THIS
-We're back.
-Recently, an elementary school student
-sent a letter to our production crew.
-That's right.
-I wonder what it's about.
-Let me read it to you for a second.
"Dear the production crew
of Chef & My Fridge."
"Thank you so much
for making such a fun program
like Chef & My Fridge."
"I bought the gummies
with my pocket money."
-Gummies?
-"Please enjoy them together."
"Sincerely, Kim Da-yul."
-Da-yul.
-Gummies?
WITH GUMMIES
SHE BOUGHT WITH HER POCKET MONEY
-They look good.
-They are.
These are so precious.
Da-yul sent these to us,
so let's try one each.
-I'll savor it.
-I should too.
Gummies mean so much to kids.
She must really like us.
There are lots.
I'll give you the rest of the box.
OH, NAM-NO…
We're eating one each.
On top of that,
Da-yul drew every one of us.
DA-YUL DREW US?
Yes, she drew us.
DREW EACH PERSON WITH LOVE
"Mr. Kim Sung-ju."
"Mr. Ahn Jung-hwan."
She drew a microphone for me
and a soccer ball for Jung-hwan.
-She added details.
-Yes.
Are those dumplings on your head?
How cute.
Nam-no's nose is shaped like a hog snout.
-Why am I so big?
-Right.
HIS BODY IS QUITE BIG…
I look like a snowman.
It's a work of art.
-At least I'm thinner than Nam-no.
-You have fried shrimp on your head.
You're right.
She spotted everyone's characteristics.
-Sung-jun's going, "Emergency."
-Emergency.
She did a great job with these details.
-I have the devil's tail.
-You have the devil's tail.
Sam has sprouts on his head.
For his naturalism.
-Is that a strawberry on Jong-won?
-A strawberry.
-For the strawberry prince.
She watched every episode.
-We have to give it our best.
-Yes, we have to try our hardest.
THANK YOU FOR THE GUMMIES
Wait, there was a PS.
"PS: Don't attack Chef Hyun-suk so much."
DA-YUL…
-Don't attack him too much.
-I guess kids feel heartbroken to see it.
Today, for Da-yul's sake,
-do not attack me at all.
-Excuse me.
Is your grandson named Da-yul?
DO NOT ATTACK MY GRANDPA
SINCERELY, GRANDSON
-He can already draw like that?
-Da-yul is a Kim.
Just like your son-in-law, right?
You're right.
He's growing way too fast.
He can already write?
So this is not your grandson?
-No?
-It's not.
If you attack me,
you will be hurting Da-yul's feelings too.
Are you going to hurt a child's--
I'm going to attack you.
PUNISHED.
LET'S ALL LISTEN TO DA-YUL TODAY
Again, for all our fans
who are giving us support,
we are in business as usual.
PLEASE DON'T WORRY
-Yes.
-We're always open.
It's time to meet today's fridge owners!
Come on out!
Who are they?
Please welcome
Cho Yeo-jeong and Ha Seok-jin.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
WELCOME
Two very good-looking guests.
They light up the studio.
The heroine of the film Parasite,
acknowledged for her talent
in Cannes and the Oscars.
Please welcome
the world-renowned actor, Cho Yeo-jeong!
-Hello.
-It's great to see you.
Her face is tinier than yours.
Right? So tiny.
Now, as for this guy,
he's a good student,
a good actor,
and a funny TV personality too.
The well-rounded "problematic" man
who can do anything.
Please welcome actor Ha Seok-jin.
-Ha Seok-jin!
-Welcome to the show.
-You were here once before, right?
-Yes, 11 years ago.
He has visited us once before,
11 years ago.
Is this your first time, Yeo-jeong?
I love to eat,
so I always watched the show
and wondered how good
the dishes they made would be.
Was there anyone
you wanted to meet in person?
-I like them all.
-I'm sure.
I really do.
But Jong-won and Nam-no…
-Hey!
-Whoa.
YOU CAN HAVE ALL THESE
ALL MY LOVE♥
When he gives up food,
it means that he's that thrilled.
-He gave me his all.
-He did.
If he gave you his food,
-it's like giving you his organs.
-You're right.
-Thank you.
-I never share my food.
-The two chefs are very different.
-Yes.
Chef Jong-won seems
organized and nicely presented,
-whereas he seems more free-spirited.
-Free-spirited.
Not neatly organized, right?
GIGGLE
-The opposite.
-I didn't mean that.
HER FAVORITES ON THE POLAR OPPOSITES
-There's a reason why they visited us.
-What is it?
-First, Seok-jin.
-Yes.
I'm starring in a KBS drama
-called Love on the Menu.
-Love on the Menu.
I see. So someone's love is on the menu.
And there, I'm playing an Italian chef.
Really?
I was hoping to learn a few things
about the career of a chef today.
The Affair Was Just the Beginning
-is the title of the show I star in.
-What was that?
The Affair Was Just the Beginning.
I'm already intrigued by the title.
It must be about affairs.
A NEW COUPLE MOVES IN NEXT DOOR
So the affair was just the beginning.
We have to resolve a much bigger case.
So we all come together like bowling pins,
and the story just unravels like crazy.
-A serial collision black comedy.
-It sounds fun.
I heard you chose this project
-because of Kim Hye-soo.
-Yes.
When I was much younger,
we were both in Royal Story: Jang Hui-bin.
I always wanted to work with her again…
-I see.
-…and I didn't want to miss the chance.
How many years has it been
-before this reunion?
-About 23 years.
IN 23 YEARS!
Were you a child actor back then?
No.
It would've been great
if I were that young now.
-When you were an infant?
-She was ten.
-Were you in it as a baby?
-Thank you.
-What do you mean? She was in the womb.
-Is that right?
WAVING IT OFF
WE'RE SAYING THAT YOU LOOK VERY YOUNG
Yeo-jeong is the reason
why one of the chefs
began to work even harder as a chef.
-What?
-She made someone here go,
-"I'll try harder!"
-Really?
"I'll be an even better chef."
"I won't be a shame
if I ever get to meet her."
-Someone was like that.
-Who?
-Jong-won.
-Really?
What's going on?
That's supposed to be my thing.
I really enjoyed watching Parasite,
and at the Blue Dragon Film Awards,
she said this as her acceptance speech
for the Best Actress Award.
"Acting always feels like
-a crush who can always leave me."
-I did.
And you said
that actually became your motivation.
I just got chills. You're right.
Because even a great actor like her
felt that way about her career,
I felt vindicated
about the way I felt about cooking.
This means Yeo-jeong
pretty much shaped Jong-won.
She has a fair share in his career.
That was quite moving. Not bad.
2ND WEEK OF SMILING FOR JONG-WON
He didn't make me laugh,
but that was moving.
-That's what he does now.
-His word resonates.
Personally,
I want to mention
what you ate in Parasite,
-Chapaguri.
-Yes.
-It was a huge hit. You have a share.
-Which is profoundly related to me.
-Yes.
-From Dad! Where Are We Going?
-I actually spread it to the world.
-You did.
-Really?
-You did that.
When I saw it on Parasite,
I was like, "Whoa, Chapaguri.
That's my Director Bong."
-And it was made with beef.
-Yes.
My gosh.
Director Bong, I inspired you.
SMUG KIM
Everyone wants credit for everything.
-That's enough.
-All right.
-Don't try to take the credit.
-Come on, Director Bong.
-Leave him alone now.
-Fine.
-I do deserve some credit.
-All right.
SOMEONE GIVE HIM A TINY SHARE…
Wasn't it delicious?
-It was.
-Right?
I rarely eat ramyeon with jjajang sauce,
so I got to use the shoot
as an excuse to enjoy it very much.
Thank you for enjoying the dish.
One second.
We spotted something very important.
-What is it?
-So this was it.
I was wondering
why these two visited us together,
and the connection was the same numbers
added at the end
of their social media account's handle.
Their handles both end
-in 0210.
-February 10th.
Seok-jin looks flustered.
-I got thirsty.
-He got thirsty.
What's going on?
We were just chatting and catching up,
and he mentioned,
"Yeo-jeong, we have the same birthday."
-It's been so long.
-It has been.
Has it been 15 years?
-No, 16.
-Wait, 16?
-We saw each other in 2010.
-Right, 2010.
My birthday on the Lunar calendar
is the same as yours.
So we found out and went,
"We were both born on February 10th."
Yes, right.
-We have the same birthday.
-Yes.
I just heard it too.
We have the same birthday.
-The same birthday?
-February 10th?
-February 10th.
-That's Sooyoung's birthday too.
SOOYOUNG'S HUBBY, THIS ISN'T THE TIME…
Have you two worked
in a drama or a show together?
I always wanted to work with her
on a drama or a film,
but I've never had the chance.
-Someone may cast them after this episode.
-After the show airs.
They seem like a good match.
They met by coincidence and found out
that they have the same birthday.
-Yes.
-And so their love story begins.
WHIPPING UP A SCENARIO
-You're writing the story?
-Yes.
And they'll eat Chapaguri together.
You're trying to get
too much credit for it.
HE'S JUST HAPPY
We meet and go,
"Zero, two, one, zero?"
IMPROVISED ACTING
That's nice. She has already started.
Yes, that's good.
Do a scene
so we can use it for the preview.
-Acting?
-"Zero, two, one, zero?"
Say, "Do you want a bowl of Chapaguri?"
CHAPAGURI KEEPS COMING BACK
Please do it for us.
You're surprised.
-Zero…
-Zero, two, one, zero?
When's your birthday?
February 10th.
Do you like Chapaguri…
Cut! Come on, Seok-jin!
What's wrong? Why did you get nervous?
That's so not like you.
Please focus, Seok-jin.
Why are we eating Chapaguri
because of the same birthday?
TOUGH TO GET INTO IT…
I know but help me out here.
You have to go with it as an actor.
One more take.
You're great, Yeo-jeong.
-Action.
-This is rough.
Is it your birthday?
Yes, wait, 0210?
February 10th?
Yes, 0210.
By any chance, do you like Chapaguri?
Yes.
With sirloin on top?
-Strip loin.
-Strip loin?
Cut! That was perfect!
THERE'S OUR PREVIEW
EXHAUSTED…
Let's move on.
To the next scene.
We're continuing?
IS IT NOT OVER YET?
That was a good take.
Our next product placement
is this beverage.
-Okay.
-The next product.
IT HELPS OUT A LOT WITH THE PRODUCTION…
-I apologize for asking to do that.
-We're sorry.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR GREAT PERFORMANCES
This is the 30th year
-since Yeo-jeong's debut.
-Are you serious?
When did she make her debut?
She first debuted
back in 1997 as a magazine model.
-For CeCi.
-CeCi.
How do you know?
CeCi?
I know what sassy is.
Back then, there were CeCi, KiKi,
and Fashionable Communication.
-They were the big three.
-That's right.
-Wasn't it Sunday Seoul?
-Back then…
Chef Hyun-suk, for you,
wasn't it Sunday Seoul?
EXACTLY WHAT HE EXPECTED…
LOL
Just now, he was saying,
"Wasn't it Sunday Seoul?"
Is that an ice cream brand?
"Sunday" or "sundae"?
There was this thick magazine
called Sunday Seoul.
I remember CeCi. That was a big one.
I was looking at it
and said, "Who is this?"
She was so beautiful.
Yeo-jeong
was already a superstar
even in her kindergarten days.
CHUCKLE
We got a picture of her.
-Whoa.
-Let's take a look.
-That's Yeo-jeong.
-Oh, no.
-That was her in the kindergarten.
-She looks the same.
-My gosh.
-How does she look that good?
-Her pupils are so huge.
-She looks like a doll.
Was that in your high school?
-My high school graduation portrait.
-The graduation picture.
What was it like when you were in school?
Just tell us the facts.
I didn't know how popular I was.
REALLY?
My father was quite strict,
so I had to go straight home after school.
Did boys call you at home?
My older sister
was also famous for her looks,
so when someone would call us at night,
my dad picked up.
Most boys would just hang up, right?
Then he'd wake us both up to scold us.
He couldn't tell who it was meant for.
-"Why does he have your number?"
-Yes.
"He has our home number?"
I can tell by the look on Eun-yeong's face
-that she can relate to her.
-Really?
-You're a twin.
-As someone who has a sister,
I can understand the difficulties
your father went through.
Because we were
the High Beams of Geumjeong-dong.
-High Beams?
Whenever we showed up,
people said we lit up the place.
Because you're so gorgeous.
Are you sure you weren't gangsters?
"The High Beams"?
-She changed lanes without signaling.
-It means something else.
THAT'S NOT IT
-We were radiant.
-The radiance.
Excuse me. Do you have proof?
I sent some to the writers.
-Let's take a look.
-Let's do that.
-Really?
-I'm serious.
The High Beams of Geumjeong-dong.
-How cute.
-Whoa.
-Is your sister on the right?
-Which one's your sister?
I'm on the left,
the one giving femme fatale vibes.
You're on the left?
-Femme fatale?
She's missing a button.
-You're right.
-The one in the middle.
-She must've fought.
-It was taken after a fight.
Her sister pulled out her button,
and Eun-yeong pulled out her hair.
A MESS…
Yes, you two must've fought.
-Yes, we didn't really get along.
-You didn't?
One of the chefs
wants to chime in
now that we're talking about looks.
What?
This one has a confession to make.
-I'll read the transcript word for word.
-The transcript?
"My looks
were actually surgically enhanced."
Surgically enhanced?
-Plastic surgery?
-A confession.
Someone had work done?
Chef Hyun-suk?
-What?
-Yes.
-You got work done?
-You did?
Where?
I didn't say I had good looks,
that I did have work done.
-Like the High Beams of Geumjeong-dong…
-The High Beams.
…people used to have nicknames
with their neighborhood.
I was the Black Mantis of Geumho-dong.
HOW FRIGHTENING…
-Black Mantis?
I used to show martial arts forms
like the praying mantis pose.
Now, here's an important piece of fact.
I had a black wart on my forehead
like a mantis's eyes.
Hence, the Black Mantis.
What was his name?
The guy who blows his nose.
-Jung Dong-nam.
-Yes, Jung Dong-nam!
Jung Dong-nam!
Can you use computer graphics on him?
TA-DA
THAT LOOKS PERFECT
So I had it removed
with a laser procedure.
You removed it completely.
-And then, my nickname changed.
-To what?
White Mantis?
Laser Choi.
-Laser Choi?
-Laser Choi of Geumho-dong.
Laser Choi.
-I probably have photos from those days.
-Photos?
-Did you turn those in?
-He did.
I see. He turned those in,
but they were pictures
after the procedure.
His Laser Choi era?
-Let's see it. Laser Choi of Geumho-dong.
-Let's see it.
-What?
-Who is that?
Is that a wart in the left photo?
You had a mole on your left cheek.
You had a wart on your cheek too?
-No, it was a mole.
-A mole.
You had a mole there?
That was the second procedure.
I'm highly lasered.
"High Laser."
Hyun-suk's looks
turned out to be surgically enhanced.
That's cool.
As you have seen
in Yeo-jeong's high school picture,
she still looks as youthful
as she did back then,
-leaving many curious.
-I'm curious.
What she always mentions is working out.
What do you do?
I always tell myself
to work out at least once a day.
I go to a modern dance studio
that I've been a member of for a while.
Or when the weather is nice,
I jog or go swimming.
-She works out a lot.
-So one of the three.
She stays disciplined
and works out a lot too.
I wonder what she keeps in her fridge.
-It's nerve-racking.
-I'm looking forward to it.
All my friends laughed at me
when I told them I'd be on the show.
They know what my fridge is like.
"Can they cook
with just carbonated water?"
Carbonated water?
They laughed at me saying,
"What can they make with club soda?"
Let's find out what Yeo-jeong eats.
-We present Yeo-jeong's fridge.
-Fridge.
-She doesn't have much.
-Wait. Emergency.
-It's too empty, right?
-Right.
She doesn't keep
a whole lot of food at home.
First of all, the top shelf
-has probiotics.
-Probiotics.
I take one on an empty stomach
with cold water in the morning.
I put it where I can see it
to make sure I remember.
How do you eat your breakfast?
I only eat blueberries for breakfast.
-Blueberries.
-Yes.
-Blueberries and…
-I see them here.
-These.
-Just these?
But I wanted something more,
so I add some ricotta
and agave syrup to them.
That sounds delicious.
People often eat those with yogurt.
My body doesn't take dairy products well.
-Lactose intolerance?
-Yes.
But I love dairy products.
When I tried ricotta,
I guess something about it
worked with me and it wasn't as bad.
That's why
I've substituted it for ricotta.
Actually, I used to eat
things like mugwort tteok for breakfast
because I love tteok, rice cake.
But then I wanted to reduce
my calorie intake even by a little,
so I've opted for blueberries.
FOR HER DIET
Then I wanted to cut down on sugar,
so it's now ricotta and olive oil.
Ricotta and olive oil?
You seem to care
about your glucose intake.
Because I have a sweet tooth.
-You have a sweet tooth?
-To cut back.
I love things like cake
or donuts.
-I love them.
-So you have a sweet tooth.
And on this side,
something's written on the bag.
"Toasted buckwheat."
"You may infuse them in hot or cold water,
or you can even pop them in like nuts."
"Buckwheat tea, 80 grams, 3,000 won."
I love buckwheat noodles,
so I even go on tours to find
good soba or buckwheat noodle places.
Soba.
So I often order
buckwheat noodles from various places,
and some restaurants
give toasted buckwheat out to customers.
I like to have it
as hot buckwheat tea in the morning,
and I even sprinkle some
on chocolate to make it crunchy.
It adds a nice bite to it.
Yes, it's deliciously nutty.
Try having it with dak-galbi,
spicy stir-fried chicken.
-Whoa.
-It's so good.
It'll feel like fried chicken, right?
We usually order fried chicken, don't we?
But if you dip dak-galbi in buckwheat,
it'll feel like that crispy skin.
It must be crispy. That sounds good.
What's this white powder?
-Buckwheat flour.
-Does it work well with your body?
Yes, I think so.
-And you like it too.
-Very much.
What can you not eat, then? First, milk.
-Not many dairy products.
-No dairy products.
-And?
-I feel bad for the chefs
because I have no meat.
-Not in my fridge.
-No meat?
-Whoa. An emergency.
-That's a first.
-No meat?
-She has no meat.
-She doesn't.
-A fridge without meat.
-This is bad.
-There's no meat.
I do like it,
but it takes a toll on my body
if I eat it too often.
-It doesn't work with her.
-I guess not.
Warming foods don't work well with me,
so I have
no garlic or onion either. Sorry.
Because of your constitution.
-No garlic, no onion.
-No onion?
-That's why you eat buckwheat.
-It cools your body.
-Cooling food for your hot constitution.
-That's right.
-What's this?
-Mung beans.
-Yes.
-How do you eat that?
-I like mung beans,
so I boil them
and eat them with fried eggs,
mixed with soy sauce.
What about when you feel like
letting loose and binge-eating?
-I eat lots.
-What do you eat?
So that does happen?
Jjajangmyeon. Ramyeon.
Pizza. I love all those.
-I see.
-Carbs.
I try to eat jjajangmyeon
and ramyeon only once a year.
-What?
-Once a year?
I can never live like that.
-Only once a year?
-Like a health checkup, once a year.
-Is it self-control?
-I decided to do that.
But starting last year,
I began to think, "Must I live like this?"
Exactly.
So maybe twice a year each.
-Twice a year.
-Wait.
My hands literally shake when I eat those.
-You must be sad afterward.
-It must be so dear.
I'm already sad while eating.
-It disappears.
-It's slowly disappearing.
It's such a shame to see it disappear
-as I eat it.
-Twice a year.
BOOHOO…
What kind of pizza do you like?
I like all kinds.
I still eat pizza from time to time.
It's too heartbreaking
to hold back on pizza, so I just eat it.
I like Italian pizza,
American pizza, Chicago pizza,
and even Korean-style.
So all kinds of pizza.
If she tries that hard to stay in shape,
-should they make healthy, low-calorie--
-No!
SO URGENT
-No.
-No?
-Not necessary?
I came here today
-to treat myself.
-A delicious dish.
I'll gladly accept high-calorie dishes.
-She'll gladly accept high-calorie dishes.
-Even desserts.
The shelf below
has some condiments.
-Gochujang.
-Traditional gochujang.
Do you enjoy Korean food?
I love it.
-Especially jeotgal, salted seafood.
-Jeotgal.
Don't people usually eat this
with carbs like rice?
Yes, so my friends tease me
and call this bizarre.
These days, there are breads
made with rice, not flour.
So I make a sandwich
and eat jeotgal as a side dish.
-To eliminate the greasiness.
-Rice bread.
Some vegetables.
Cucumber, celery, cilantro,
chamnamul, bracken, and cabbage.
You must like fruit.
-Yes, like peaches, cherries, and plums.
-Peaches, plums.
-Cherries.
-And figs.
-I like seasonal fruit, like peaches now.
-Seasonal fruit.
She likes seasonal fruit.
On this side,
-pomegranate vinegar and omija cheong.
-She has lots of cheong.
I see some vinegar
and similar things here.
This was the first time I realized
I had so many kinds of vinegar
in my fridge.
I like that sour note.
-You like sourness.
-Yes.
I take those in various ways.
As for the pomegranate vinegar
and lemon vinegar,
I drink it when I crave beer
-by mixing club soda with cheong.
-By mixing it.
And I enjoy it while watching a movie.
It's a beer substitute.
You already have some beer.
Is it necessary to make that?
Those are for guests.
You don't drink it yourself?
May I take some?
She serves it to her guests
when she invites them over.
We're her guests now.
GIGGLING
-For your house guests.
-Yes.
-What are those laundry soap shapes?
-Laundry soap?
-Laundry soap? These?
-Yes.
Those are cookies I got as a present.
-Cookies.
-Yes.
Why would she keep
laundry soap in the fridge?
SILENT…
-He's old enough to remember soaps.
-Are you
trying to hurt Da-yul?
Why would she keep laundry soap in here?
He used to do the laundry out by a stream.
-Out by a stream?
-A stream?
BACK IN THE DAY…
What's this next to the beer?
-It's trouble. I've never opened it.
-What is it?
"Wolfgang Puck"?
-Wolfgang Puck is a chef.
-The steak house.
Back in 2020
when I went to the Academy Awards,
that was probably a souvenir
given out to everyone attending.
-It's probably chocolate.
-Chocolate.
May we open it?
Sure.
-The chocolate for the Oscar attendees.
-It's gold.
Has it been six years?
-It's shaped like the statuette.
-How cool.
It's such a shame to eat it.
I wouldn't be able to.
-So only the attendees got these?
-Yes.
I'll put it back in the fridge.
Let's check out the freezer.
I see some seafood.
-Shrimp. Mackerel.
-Mackerel.
-Squid. Octopus.
-She has lots of seafood.
FULL OF SEAFOOD
Seafood tends to be my main ingredient.
She doesn't eat meat.
-No.
-Does it work with you?
Yes, I like seafood.
How do you eat this octopus?
That's one of the reasons why I came.
I really like octopus,
-but it's hard to work with.
-It's tough to cook octopus.
So I wanted to ask you
for tips on how to eat octopus.
You should either cook it
for a very long time or very briefly.
-Either one.
-Really?
I SEE
Please use this octopus.
That was her constitution-friendly fridge,
and we're done looking through.
Everything is constitution-friendly.
Then what is she hoping to eat today?
Let's find out her orders.
Show us.
Yeo-jeong's Constitution-Friendly Journey.
How cool. Her name sounds like "journey."
-She sticks to the constitutional diet.
-What I eat
consists of usual ingredients
prepared in the same way.
I wanted to try delicious dishes made with
ingredients friendly to my constitution.
-That's it.
-I wanted to see how it goes.
All right. What's the second order?
The second one.
Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
Then what's next?
Was that just the beginning?
I don't think self-discipline matters
on a day like this.
I don't care if it's high in calories.
I'll consider this my cheat day
and eat something really good.
All right.
She disclosed both her orders.
Take a look at the orders
and choose to participate.
I'll go.
Self-discipline
hasn't even begun in my life,
which you can probably tell by my shape.
I'll go for the second order…
Stop touching.
-I'll go for the second one.
-Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
All right. Good call.
-He took a spot.
-Challenge your mortal enemy.
No, I'd never take that spot.
-I'll go.
-Ho-young?
WHICH ONE?
-Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
-Really?
I'll show you
what I had to do to turn out like me.
I don't think she'd want that though.
Poong and Ho-young will fight in the round
Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
WOW♥
Someone must take
her constitution-friendly journey.
Any volunteers?
-I knew it.
-Of course.
I saw in her fridge
that she had many ingredients
I also liked, so I'll cook with those.
He'll join your journey.
We need one more.
Then I'll go.
-Hey.
-Wait.
-Did you read that right?
-He read it wrong again.
She's not asking you
to keep your constitution as is.
It's not my constitution?
Not the greater Yang type.
OH, IS THAT SO?
Are you in, Nam-no?
She showed me a bit of favor,
-so I want to cook for her.
-All right.
-He's in.
-Thank you.
Everything has been decided.
So let us begin
Jong-won and Nam-no's round!
This is the first round of cook-off
with Yeo-jeong's ingredients.
Two of her favorite chefs
are up against each other.
The organized one, Chef Son Jong-won,
versus the messy one, Chef Yoon Nam-no.
Can we consider
the winner of this round your bias?
-Sure.
-Okay.
-It won't be easy.
-Yes, of course.
The thing is, even after combining
last year and this year's result,
Jong-won has never lost once
against Nam-no.
-He won all rounds.
-So far.
The topic for this round
is a constitution-friendly diet.
Out of concern,
let me ask one question to Nam-no
before we begin.
What's Yeo-jeong's body constitution?
She had mentioned it earlier.
Tell me.
She has a colder body.
-"Colder body"?
-You're wrong.
-It's the opposite.
-She has a naturally hot constitution.
She has internal heat.
She has a hotter body,
so she eats food that cools it down.
I understood.
Which ingredients does she like?
-Buckwheat.
-Yes.
-And no dairy products.
-That's correct.
-She prefers seafood, no meat.
-Yes.
You're right.
He remembered it well.
FEELING PROUD
Jong-won, you also eat ramyeon
only once a year?
Yes, I also eat ramyeon
around once a year.
I haven't had it this year,
and I really get you.
-He'll have it later this year.
-You understand her.
Another thing I connected with
was that I also drink club soda
when I crave spicy food.
-You do?
-When I'm stressed out.
When I'm bored,
I drink club soda with lemon flavoring.
FEELING DISTANT…
And that's his off day.
-He's like me.
-He's very disciplined.
CHEF NAM-NO'S INGREDIENTS:
TOASTED BUCKWHEAT, BUCKWHEAT FLOUR
MUNG BEAN, CHICKPEA, CORN, SHRIMP, SQUID
POLLACK ROE, MUGWORT TTEOK, AND MORE
Chef Nam-no, what are you making?
I'm making
Will Win a Star With Buckwheat.
Will Win a Star.
-Will Win a Star.
-You have a dialect.
-Yes.
The Gangwon-do dialect.
I prepared two dishes
made with lots of buckwheat,
which Yeo-jeong loves very much.
First, buckwheat crêpe.
-I see.
-Buckwheat crêpe.
-Sounds great.
-It's usually
filled with ripe kimchi and pork,
but I'll use seafood today.
-I see.
-That sounds good.
Next, I'll use corn
and make cold soup.
-Sounds good.
-Cold soup?
There's a French potato soup
called vichyssoise.
Instead of potatoes,
I'll use corn, chickpea, and oat milk.
-Sounds good.
-I'll use those three
-to make the cold soup.
-I see.
You'll stop by Gangwon-do,
then go to France.
CHEF JONG-WON'S INGREDIENTS:
TOASTED BUCKWHEAT, MUNG BEAN
RICE BREAD, COOKIE, PEACH, PLUM,
FIG, LEMON, OMIJA CHEONG, AND MORE
Up against him is Chef Jong-won,
what are you making?
When I saw you sitting there,
you reminded me of a fairy,
or even an elf.
He's talking smooth again.
THE ELOQUENCE THAT CAPTURED JUNG-HWAN
-Nam-no has already lost.
-You do that a lot now.
He called her fairy, yojeong,
not Yeo-jeong.
-Like Tinkerbell.
-Tinkerbell.
I want to accompany a fairy like you
as we take a journey for desserts.
-No way.
-Desserts.
Here's the name of my dish.
Born a Fairy, Yeo-jeong,
Eat This Dessert and Pick Your J.
I see.
That's lengthy.
It was too long.
What's this dish like?
-I prepared two dishes.
-Two dishes.
-First, a tart.
-Tart.
In the tart,
I will add flan,
which is a type of custard.
A flan for dessert.
It's now summer,
so fresh fruit is in season.
And these fruit aren't high in sugar,
so you can enjoy them
without feeling guilty.
Doesn't flan take a while to make?
It does, but the method I'm using
involves a microwave,
so it'll be quite easy to make.
-There's a way?
-And next,
I'll make a traditional beverage
called omi-galsu.
It means "water that quenches thirst."
It's made with either mung beans
or soybean juice.
-Really?
-I'll use mung beans.
Like misugaru, the grain drink.
So I'll use your omija cheong
and make two different items.
-His focus is on dessert.
-Misugaru.
All right, then. Let us begin this round.
I'm nervous.
"Cho Yeo-jeong has brought me up."
Crushing on cooking, Chef Son Jong-won.
But he says, "Please bring me up too."
Crushing on stars, Chef Yoon Nam-no.
Which one of them
will become Yeo-jeong's favorite?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Who'll become her bias?
Begin!
THE BIAS SHOWDOWN
Who'll become her favorite, her bias?
-Syrup?
-Jong-won or Nam-no?
They have two distinct styles.
If you fail to make flan once,
then you're done.
-Really?
-There's no going back.
-It takes a while too.
-I see.
He'll have to use all 15 minutes,
checking in every now and then.
Flan isn't easy to make.
-Chef Jong-won is flattening the bread.
-That's the rice bread.
-The rice bread.
-Yes.
It'll probably turn into a tart shell.
He's making the tart shell
with rice bread?
-Yes, you can often use bread.
-No way.
Nam-no looks busy on the blender.
-It's buckwheat.
-Buckwheat.
-It's the crêpe batter.
-For the crêpe.
He's using buckwheat flour.
-He's making the buckwheat crêpe.
-He's making the batter now?
Done.
OAT MILK
CHICKPEA
The corn.
Nam-no's using corn.
Why do you have to taste so many things?
He's blending that with corn.
That's something else.
The first one was for the crêpe.
-The second is for the corn soup.
-The beverage.
-He's adding ricotta.
-Ricotta.
-Ricotta?
-Because it's soup?
He said it'd be like something
between porridge and soup.
STRAINING THROUGH A SIEVE
Nam-no looks dead serious.
-He is.
-You should take Jong-won down.
It's about time.
-He'd better win today.
-Yes.
THINLY PRESSED RICE BREAD
REMOVING JUST THE CRUST
CUT IN HALF!
-He's putting them together.
-Huh?
-It was small, so he's connecting them.
-He's sticking them together.
Because the bread itself was too small?
-The egg wash?
-What are you brushing on it?
-I'm buttering it.
-Butter.
He puts butter on it and makes it bigger.
To make it bigger?
If you like it,
I wanted you to take some home.
HEHE
-He'll pack some for you.
-And sit in her fridge.
YAY
CHUCKLE…
He's now very good
at making his case with the guests.
Nam-no, anything to-go?
Nam-no.
-No, he has to eat the rest.
-Nam-no.
-Yes?
-He's offering something to-go.
I'll make sure you take mine too.
-It's okay.
-Will she have leftovers?
I have a great feeling today.
-He says he has a great feeling.
-Whoa.
It must be good.
STILL MAKING THE TART SHELL
He's spending a while on that.
He's putting it in a mold.
-A pie mold.
It's big.
I didn't think he'd do it with rice bread.
He's using bread to make that.
How creative.
BUT…
Are you burning the syrup intentionally?
It's burning.
-What's burning?
-No.
-Caramel.
-He's making caramel.
Is that dalgona?
-No?
-It's caramel.
-Is that burnt?
-It's too early to be happy.
-Wait.
-It's burnt.
-It smells burnt.
No, that's burnt.
It's too early for him to be happy. No.
It looks perfect.
If it's brown, it's burnt.
No, it's perfect.
-He has to do it over.
-Sung-jun says it's perfect.
-That's caramel?
-Is that okay?
-It's caramel.
What are those? What kind of beans?
They're like stones.
-Pie weights.
-It makes sure the sheet doesn't rise.
Without it, it can either rise or pop.
Did you press start?
Press start.
I practically made that.
-Chef Sung-jun…
-I saved it.
…I'm rather grateful today.
But rice bread,
as opposed to regular bread,
is much denser and heavier,
so it doesn't really rise.
-I see. But don't let it rise.
-But still…
How do you know these things?
I just pick up things.
It's nice to hear his comments here,
but when you're out there,
he's just a huge nuisance.
A BITTER REMARK…
And you're too busy to correct him
when he spreads false info.
YOU'RE SO RIGHT
Especially when he makes a scene
over a small mishap,
as if I've committed a huge crime.
-It's burning!
-"It's really burnt!"
Make one mistake, and I will point it out.
Is that the crêpe?
Make it thin, Nam-no.
-That's nice.
-That's important.
-He's making buckwheat crêpes.
-That's good.
If you use only buckwheat,
it'll rip much more easily,
so it looks like
he added some flour or starch.
Make them thin. Nice job.
Five minutes have gone by, ten left.
EGG
ONE MORE
3. BEAT EGGS, ADD OAT MILK AND SUGAR
He's making the flan base.
-That's flan?
-That's the flan base.
Jong-won's making flan.
Flan.
BUTTER THE BOWL
ABOUT TO ADD CARAMEL, BUT…
-Argh.
-What?
-It's an emergency.
-It hardened.
-I told you so. It's ruined.
-It's solid.
-What now?
-It's your time.
-That's ruined.
He left it over iced water,
so the caramel hardened.
It's made of sugar,
so it becomes solid when cooled.
Microwave.
-I see.
-Here's what flan is.
It's similar to pudding,
and the caramel sauce on top
is supposed to drizzle down.
But that became solid.
Microwave.
-Sometimes it goes over a tart, right?
-Yes.
-That's flan.
-It melted.
-It did? Okay.
-Wow.
He quickly melted it.
It'd better not mix with water.
If it does, it'll stay runny.
-Will it turn out like pudding?
-Syrup is heavier, so it'll sink.
I guess he's putting plastic on it.
He put plastic wrap on it and made holes.
I guess he can make it faster
if he uses the microwave.
-It's usually cooked in a double boiler.
-It needs to be a double boiler.
Eight minutes and ten seconds.
-Oh, gosh.
-What's Nam-no doing?
NAM-NO IS VERY FOCUSED TODAY
Nam-no looks completely focused.
CHOPPED GREEN ONION
-He's adding shrimp too.
-He chopped them into small pieces.
He's mixing pollack roe, shrimp, and corn
to make the crêpe filling.
I see. The stuffing?
-He added shrimp too.
-Yes.
He added corn and squid too.
That has to be delicious.
-It reminds me of okonomiyaki.
-Yes.
TIME TO FLIP THE CRÊPE
FLY UP
THEN LAND!
It looks nice.
NOTHING BURNT, LOOKS PERFECT
It looks so nice.
Excellent!
You might win a star today.
It's promising.
Must be going well for Nam-no.
He's in a good mood.
Things are going well.
Nam-no's dish is smooth sailing.
What are you pouring in?
-Olive oil.
Olive oil is good for you.
-Right.
-It won't make you fat.
-And it goes with her body constitution.
-Yes.
What did you add to the blender, Jong-won?
-Mung beans.
I guess that's for the omi-galsu.
-That?
-A beverage to quench your thirst.
It'll make you thirstier.
That's so little.
ARE YOU ON MY SIDE OR NOT?
He's mixing omija cheong and mung beans.
Fresh cream?
-Ricotta.
Why is he whipping ricotta?
-It'll make it softer.
-It becomes softer?
CREAM INTO A PIPING BAG!
She said she likes ricotta.
Six minutes and fifty seconds.
-You have under seven minutes.
-Oh, gosh.
DROPPING THE STUFFING IN A PAN
-Looks good.
-That looks good.
-It has to be good.
-It looks great.
-He added the buckwheat.
-The toasted buckwheat?
-Oyster sauce.
The crêpe stuffing looks really good.
He's on a roll today.
JONG-WON IS RIGHT BEHIND HIM
GRINDING SOMETHING
-What's that? Cookies?
-That looks good.
Cookies?
Did you just grind
the cookies she got as a gift?
The ones Hyun-suk called soap.
-Yes.
-The soap bars.
I mixed them with buckwheat.
-Sounds good.
-Whoa.
-No way.
A peach.
CUTTING OUT JUST THE FLESH
So you can cut it out like that?
Mom's going to get mad
if you do that at home.
-For wasting so much.
-Yes, Mom would get mad.
I do this at home,
give it to my mom, and I eat the rest.
The good son's cut.
-The good son's cut?
-Good parts are for my mom.
The good son's cut.
-Plums?
-And the same for plums.
Whoa.
Figs.
LEMON ZEST
-It's so pretty.
-So you can cut it like that?
Sung-ju, five minutes.
Can you report from the kitchen?
-Oh, gosh!
-Let me go check.
-Please.
-I'm on my way.
Time truly does fly.
It's so scary.
-My gosh. Can they really finish?
-What now?
Jong-won and Nam-no.
-Nam-no is at a good pace.
-His crêpe looks great.
He used lots of buckwheat and seafood.
Will he win a star with buckwheat or not?
I think he will!
NAM-NO'S BUCKWHEAT FLOWERS WILL BLOOM
-I think he will!
-Will he win today?
-It tastes like something she'd like.
-Really?
There's a nice bite to it too.
-Those are mung beans.
-You used them, right?
This is really good.
Just make sure this turns out nicely.
It'd probably benefit Chef Nam-no
if I ate his dishes first.
That's dessert, so, right?
Will it be Jong-won or Nam-no?
They have completely different styles.
-This must be the omija thing.
-Omi-galsu?
-I'll add sparkling water.
-Sparkling water.
-It's a modern version.
It's a modern version
of a traditional beverage.
Let me try the omi-galsu
with 3 minutes and 8 seconds left.
Tell us what it's like, Sung-ju!
It's tangy and delicious!
GIGGLING
That's nice.
Will the gal
give me a star for this galsu?
That kind of start surely deserves a star.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT
The flan is out.
-Flan.
-Galsu!
It's still hot.
COOLING OVER ICED WATER
THIS TIME, THE OVEN
-For the tart.
-These are ready.
THE RICE BREAD TART SHELL
-Don't eat these. You'll chip your teeth.
-Not these.
-Sung-ju.
-Yes?
Try it and see if it's a stone.
I'm not supposed to.
It's an emergency.
-The weights won't fall out.
-One more time.
AN UNEXPECTED EMERGENCY
-It's an emergency.
-Emergency!
-No!
-You have 2 minutes and 14 seconds.
That's still hot, Jong-won.
-It's an emergency.
-Don't do that!
-It's still hot!
-Jong-won, it's hot!
-It's probably still hot!
-It's too hot!
EMERGENCY
Why is he holding that?
SHE FINALLY NOTICED…
He's doing this for Yeo-jeong!
-It's hot.
-It's still hot.
-I got this.
-He sacrifices his fingers.
-It's ready.
-It looks nice.
-It's just a little ripped.
-It turned out nicely.
Oh, my gosh.
Things look smooth for Nam-no.
PLATING THE MUGWORT TTEOK
COOLED CORN SOUP
-Is that soup? No?
-Yes, it's cold soup.
SLURP
THE REMAINDER GOES INTO HIS MOUTH
This has to turn out well.
Make sure you roll it up nicely.
-That squid seems too big.
-What?
I don't think I can roll this up.
ROLLING UP
SUCCESS
That looks nice, Nam-no.
It looks good.
YUMMY
-That looks good.
-It does.
It's impossible to be bad.
It looks good.
CELERY
TOASTED BUCKWHEAT
FINISHING UP WITH CELERY AND BUCKWHEAT
-One minute.
-One minute and ten seconds.
-Is this ricotta?
-One minute. Emergency.
-Ricotta.
-It's a little ripped.
That's ground cookies
and buckwheat, right?
It's all about the flan.
It has to turn out well.
-The flan.
-What now?
-Water got in.
Water got in!
See? I told you that water got in!
Why is there water in it?
-Emergency!
-It's an emergency.
Things aren't going well for Jong-won.
IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY FOR NAM-NO
Nam-no, try just a little harder,
and you might win.
Nam-no finishes!
THAT'S INSANE
Chef Nam-no was on a roll this time.
NOW JONG-WON HAS TO FINISH!
ATTEMPTING TO PLATE
BY FLIPPING IT UPSIDE-DOWN
You have to flip it well!
GASP
You have to flip it well.
No! It fell apart!
WHAT WILL HE DO NOW?
-Oh, no!
-I can't believe it.
-Is that really flan?
-Is that soft tofu or what?
I CAN'T WATCH ANYMORE…
HOW WILL HE DEAL WITH THIS?
He'll cover it with fruit anyway.
-The flan got ruined.
-Cover it up with fruit!
Cover everything up.
HIDDEN
Jong-won fell into trouble.
How will he get out of this?
He's covering everything
with seasonal fruit.
It's a big emergency.
-Ten.
-Nine.
Eight.
-Seven. Six.
-Oh, no.
-Five. Four. Three.
-Two. One.
Jong-won is done too.
He's done too.
-Gosh.
-That was insane.
This place really is a battleground.
It's like a sports game.
-My hands and feet got cold.
-Really?
My hands and feet are frozen.
-The dishes are finished.
-How do I eat these?
Everything got ready, after all.
These all look great.
Everything has been made for Yeo-jeong.
How do they cope
with this kind of pressure?
Right? These are amazing chefs.
First, please try Chef Nam-no's dish,
Will Win a Star With Buckwheat.
HEALTHY GANGWON-DO DISHES
MADE WITH BUCKWHEAT
HEARTY SEAFOOD BUCKWHEAT CRÊPE
GANGWON-DO MEETS FRANCE, COLD CORN SOUP
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S
WILL WIN A STAR WITH BUCKWHEAT
Crêpe first?
-No, please try the soup first.
-The soup first.
-I put her favorite tteok on the bottom.
-You did?
-Have a sip, then eat it with the tteok.
-A sip first.
-First, a sip. Okay.
-And then with a spoon.
-He put tteok in here?
It's a mix of Gangwon-do and France.
SIP
It reminds me of Korean soups too.
SAVORING CAREFULLY
It's good.
-She's careful.
-I was scared.
She doesn't just go, "Man, this is good."
-She's not an old dude.
-No.
It'd be weird if she said, "Man, so good."
I do that when I drink hot soup.
I saw you working with my favorite tteok.
This used to be her breakfast.
HER BREAKFAST TTEOK'S MAKEOVER
-Whoa.
-Yes?
-We got a "whoa."
-Must be good.
-Hmm?
-They must go well.
Was there an unexpected twist?
Why does it taste zesty like fruit?
I just had tteok.
I added a dash of lemon zest.
LEMON ZEST FOR TANG
AND TRUFFLE SEASONING
You're like a magician.
She asked, "Why is this tteok zesty?"
She seems surprised.
But the corn flavor isn't too strong.
-So it's corn and…
-Chickpeas.
-And then what?
-Oat milk.
Chickpeas are so good for you.
-What's it like?
-It's so good.
-It's so good?
-Yes.
Does it taste nutty?
It does.
Yet it's so tangy,
thanks to the lemon zest.
-Hey.
-It's not too rich.
Great job with that.
Just by looking at it,
I expected it to only taste
clean and nutty.
So that tang must've been a twist.
Yes, and the mugwort flavor.
It's absolutely delicious.
I want a huge batch of it.
She wants a huge batch of it.
I'll make you this much.
Please pack some up to-go.
Next, the mung bean and buckwheat crêpe.
He considered your constitution
and made sure
the dish didn't go overboard.
Also, it's less greasy
than your usual buckwheat crêpes.
-It looks clean.
-It would be.
Should I eat it with chopsticks?
If you can, in one bite.
-In one bite?
-It might be difficult for her.
-Can she fit that into her mouth?
-I can.
-She'll give it a try.
-Is it too big?
TOTALLY POSSIBLE
She eats very well.
Mmm!
YES!
She sounds amazed.
AN APPLAUSE
-What?
-Do you like it?
-It's so good.
-Is it that good?
It's very clean.
I also love squid sundae,
and it reminds me of that too.
You're right. I used squid.
She must like it.
On top of that, toasted buckwheat
adds such a nice texture.
It's fantastic. I mean it.
Thank you.
It's such a wonder
that you can still talk so well
with food in your mouth.
If it were us, it'd fly everywhere.
-And her pronunciation is right on.
-I was surprised.
-She clearly had food in her mouth.
-She was chewing.
Because I have to do lines
while eating sometimes.
SO SHE ENUNCIATES
-Yes.
-I knew it.
-That's what you do as an actor.
-Right? We could never do that.
I had to read my lines while eating
in the Chapaguri scene too.
Yes, you were eating.
-It's a wonder.
-I think I remember.
-If it were us, it'd fly out.
-Everywhere.
-It'd be a mess.
-We can't keep it in.
GLAD SHE'S EATING ALONE
-Nam-no actually stayed focused today.
-He did.
I caught you with my piggy data network.
-Piggy data.
-Wait.
-Will Nam-no finally win against Jong-won?
-It's so good.
He'll probably get lots of points.
-It was so good.
-Please try Jong-won's dish now.
FLAN TOPPED WITH SEASONAL FRUIT
FOR THE DESSERT FAIRY
OMI-GALSU TO BEAT THE HEAT
AND RECHARGE ENERGY
BORN A FAIRY, YEO-JEONG,
EAT THIS DESSERT AND PICK YOUR J
How should she eat this?
Mung beans help greatly with digestion.
-Have a sip of the beverage first.
-The beverage first.
-Isn't the color gorgeous?
-Omi-galsu.
The color suits her.
Yes, it fits her image.
-Whoa.
-Must be refreshing.
This is…
-This is so good.
-I see.
-It must make a nice starter.
-I knew it.
Omija means
that it has five different flavor notes,
and it's a great partner to mung beans.
I guess omija and mung beans go well.
I must've become thirsty
while watching them cook.
It must be good. She keeps going for it.
Omija and mung beans.
She's almost done with it.
That's galsu.
Mung beans don't taste dry.
I squeezed out just its juice.
-I squeezed it out.
-Just the juice.
You did that in that short while?
Did you add sparkling water?
It's omija cheong, mung bean juice,
boiled, cooled,
then I added some sparkling water
since you seemed to like it.
That's why it feels like champagne.
I can probably try to make this.
-That's nice.
-Because she doesn't drink.
-It's really good.
-She seems impressed.
How about this?
-Everything to the bottom.
-I should have everything, right?
-The pie.
-There was trouble with his flan,
but he covered it up with fruit.
It's the same once you eat it.
Thankfully, this was the first time
I had heard of flan,
-so it's fine.
-Is it?
-Is it like pudding?
-Yes, it's pretty much pudding.
-All right.
-She already looks happy.
Yes, she has a sweet tooth,
but she had been holding herself back.
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
MMM
CAN'T HIDE HER HAPPINESS
Buckwheat, emergency.
-I'm astonished at the dessert right away.
-Right? It comes to you so naturally.
You can taste that sweetness.
I don't know if this is right
because I haven't had flan before,
but with the rice bread you used,
it's like a really delicious French toast
I can have as a meal.
It tastes more like a meal.
It's so good.
I guess it's more than a dessert
-if she says it could be a meal.
-Yes.
She thinks she could have this as a meal.
Mmm.
We thought Nam-no would win easily,
but there was a bit of a twist.
What's this jam?
Blueberry jam and whipped ricotta.
He added some at the end.
He tried his best
with blueberry jam and ricotta.
It'd make a good breakfast, right?
I often make French toast,
along with blueberry jam
or actual berries,
as well as some ricotta.
This seems like
a luxurious version of that.
How am I supposed to choose?
-That's up to you.
-This is too cruel.
-That's the point.
You can continue to try them
before you decide.
-She should.
-They are too different.
Do you have some for Seok-jin?
CHEF NAM-NO'S DISH FIRST
No way.
Seok-jin may have a different taste.
-He said to sip this first.
-Sip it first.
Chef Nam-no's dishes.
-What's this face?
-He's pleased.
It smelled like fruit,
but it tastes like legumes in my mouth.
It must be a wonder to you.
NEXT, WITH THE MUGWORT TTEOK
Mugwort tteok.
He found a piece of tteok inside.
Isn't the tteok good?
Don't force anything.
Because I love mugwort tteok.
FORCING HIM
It could've been
a bit boring if it were just this soup,
but this tteok
adds a hearty side to the soup.
HEARTY
Did you notice a bit of France?
You should be there too.
I'm not so sure about the location.
-It's just good.
-It's good.
Also,
it reached a part of my brain
that has never experienced this flavor.
REVIEWING LIKE AN ENGINEERING MAJOR
The buckwheat crêpe.
SMILES BIG AS SOON AS HE EATS IT
It must be that good.
This feels so good.
I'm not sure about going to Paris,
but I did a layover in Bangkok.
AN EXPECTED LAYOVER
-It's the celery.
-It must be the celery.
There's this vague Southeast Asian feel.
It's seasoned to perfection.
When you imagine a healthy dish,
you think of something
that doesn't taste that good.
But that's not the case here at all.
That's the best, then.
If it's both delicious and healthy,
that's simply the best.
Next, Chef Jong-won's dishes.
-Try the omi-galsu first.
-Omi-galsu.
-It's a traditional beverage.
-Huh?
-Man.
-Isn't it good?
-There goes the old dude. "Man."
-The old dude?
-Whoa.
He goes, "Man,"
while having some beverage.
He's one of us now.
It tastes like royal court cuisine.
-It must taste traditional.
-The omija.
It has that flavor.
And next.
She ate it like this, right?
Everything together.
He tried to make flan.
Does everything go well together?
Mmm.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
It tastes Gen Z.
-Like Gen Z?
-Gen Z?
Is that positive or negative?
It's something trendy restaurants
tend to sell.
-Right.
-I see.
-Like a place in Seongsu-dong.
-A hip area.
Sexy food.
-Sexy food?
-This is bad.
It's like a place
popular with influencers,
so I took a bite without expecting much,
but I'm left thinking, "Well, it is good."
He's much better at commenting.
This is sad for me.
FEELING BAD
-I should've talked like him.
-It's all right.
And now, please make a decision.
-Oh, gosh.
-It's a difficult decision to make.
Press one for Son Jong-won
and two for Nam-no.
Make your decision
and press the button!
PUSH
-I did.
-You did?
You said it was too cruel.
-It is.
-You said it was difficult.
-But she chose quickly.
-That was quick.
Which one did Yeo-jeong choose?
Let's find out!
Jong-won currently has ten stars.
Nam-no has two.
And Jong-won has never lost to Nam-no.
A constitution-friendly journey!
Who did you choose?
Who helped Yeo-jeong
with her constitution-friendly diet?
Who is it?
SON JONG-WON WINS
JONG-WON WINS
-Jong-won wins.
-I can't believe it.
Son Jong-won.
He's strong against Nam-no.
WON ALL 5 ROUNDS AGAINST NAM-NO
Everything was good,
but it was the fact that
Chef Jong-won decided to make dessert.
That was a huge plus for me.
I love desserts so much,
but I usually have to hold back.
But if I eat this as a meal,
I'd be satisfied after this.
It'd be a meal for me, and it was so good.
Nam-no's dish
calls for that dessert after.
-You can eat more after.
-I wanted dessert.
-She can't stay in shape, then.
-It was good.
This means her bias is Jong-won now.
Let's hear it from him.
It was such an honor
for me to cook for an actor
who gave me such a big comfort.
Thank you for enjoying the dish.
Please put a star on him.
-This is his 11th win.
-Whoa.
The sole 1st place with 11 wins.
WIDENING THE GAP
Yeo-jeong chose you.
Congratulations.
-Let's take ten.
-Let's take ten minutes off.
Should I just eat this?
It was so good.
GIVING UP THE BREAK
Oh, then…
Min-hyeong!
CALLS SOMEONE OVER
YEO-JEONG'S MANAGER
SHARES WITH THE MANAGER
It's so good.
Doesn't it remind you of squid sundae?
And have a sip of this.
-Are you done with this?
-Yes.
It's really good.
CHUGS
Why are you drinking that?
That was really good.
AS ALWAYS, FINISHED THE LEFTOVERS
Let us begin the second cook-off
with Yeo-jeong's ingredients.
The leading authority
of cheat day meals on the show,
-Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
-"Leading authority"?
He's up against Chef Jung Ho-young,
whose every day is a cheat day.
Poong poses a huge problem to Ho-young.
You've only lost against him recently,
putting you at four straight losses.
-Really?
OUT OF HIS ELEMENT WHEN FACING POONG
-Did you think he'd be too easy?
-How shocking.
I ran into him a few days ago
outside the studio,
and he was such an eyesore
for some reason.
But I didn't know why,
so I thought about it.
Understandable.
It's partially for my recent losses,
and partially because of his smugness.
SMUG ABOUT HIS STARS
We received a transcript.
He'll be a bigger eyesore after this.
"To me,
Ho-young's level of Poongphobia
is as high as Nam-no's."
So Ho-young and Nam-no
are the same to you?
He's a star opener for me.
-A star opener?
-Like a bottle opener.
-Oh, my.
-A star opener.
-Aka an easy win.
-Yes.
I can tell by his face
that he feels winning is a given.
It's now about how big a win
he gets against him.
An overwhelming win.
A dramatic win.
A buzzworthy win.
-It's all about the buzzworthiness.
-Yes.
Ho-young will lose today.
FULL OF ANXIETY
-You seem rather grim.
-Make your case too.
If it were the old days,
I would've stepped in and said something,
but after consecutive losses,
I think I can understand Nam-no.
-I've been feeling small lately.
-Don't be.
Actually, my relationship
with my wife isn't so great
after my consecutive losses.
-You're bringing your family into this?
-His family.
FAMILY DISPUTE(?) DUE TO HIS LOSSES
Our biggest fights break out
whenever I lose to Poong.
She's like, "Aren't you ashamed?"
I'm rather worried right now.
THE PEACE IN HIS FAMILY IS AT STAKE
WEBTOON ARTIST POONG'S INGREDIENTS:
CUCUMBER, LEMON, HONEY, RICOTTA
What are you making today, Poong?
The name of my dish is
Pizza Nation, Princess Yeo-jeong.
-Pizza?
-Pizza Nation, Princess Yeo-jeong.
Oh, gosh.
-She said she loves pizza.
-This is cheating.
-So, pizza?
-Emergency.
The only time I make pizza
is when our guest is someone
who brought glory to our nation.
-I always made pizza.
-I'll leave this out here.
-He only makes it then.
-Yes.
HIS BEGINNING IS ALWAYS HUMBLE
BUT HIS WORKS ALWAYS END SUCCESSFULLY
-Those who brought glory to us.
-Those who did that.
-She did that through Parasite…
-And she did just that.
-…so it was about time I made pizza.
-So she's on that level.
On top of that, she said she likes pizza.
What I'm making today
is a cucumber pizza.
-Cucumber pizza?
-Cucumber?
Will it be okay?
I'll use cucumbers to--
-Turn it off.
-It's already an emergency.
-Hear me out first.
First, I'll make cucumber cream.
-Cucumber cream?
-Cucumber cream? Even worse.
These days, there are baguettes
filled with salted cucumber,
-like a sandwich.
-Something like that.
-It's the trend.
-Yes, you might've seen that,
but I am literally
turning cucumber into cream.
NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN CUCUMBER CREAM!
-So you won't see cucumber shapes?
-There will be a few.
I'm topping it with a layer of pickles.
ARGH
Also, the pizza dough will be deep-fried.
-Deep-fried?
-Deep-fried pizza?
RIGHT…
You're only thinking of online buzz.
No, it'll be good.
-Seok-jin isn't convinced either.
-Not by those words.
It's hard to imagine.
Many people are shaking their heads.
Is Poong going too far?
-No.
-A cucumber pizza.
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
OCTOPUS, SQUID, SHRIMP, POLLACK ROE
MOZZARELLA, CUCUMBER,
TOASTED BUCKWHEAT, LEMON, CILANTRO
Chef Ho-young, you're up against him,
so what are you making?
The dish I'm making
is for Yeo-jeong, the pretty girl.
I'm making stir-fried udon
with freshly pulled udon noodles.
-Fresh udon noodles?
-I saw seafood in your fridge,
so I'll use shrimp and squid,
then top it with pollack roe.
-He won already.
-I saw that
-she had octopus, so I'll make it tender…
-Octopus.
…and mix it with vinegar,
soy sauce, and lemon juice…
-That's his winning recipe.
-…for you to enjoy
tangy and creamy flavors at the same time.
Both dishes sound
equally delicious.
Pizza has always been my favorite,
so I even called it cheating,
but udon is also something
that I hold back from eating.
The udon already sounds so good.
It's been long since I've had it.
Do you want to decide first?
ALREADY DECIDED TO GO WITH UDON(?)
URGENT
-Mine is a dessert pizza.
-A dessert pizza.
-I see. A dessert pizza.
Because you thought she prefers desserts.
-So you jumped on it.
-I'm not always like that.
-I saw you doing that just now.
-She seems to vote for the dessert.
Come to think of it,
I'm serving the octopus as dessert.
-Octopus?
-Octopus dessert?
-Really?
JUST HAVING FUN
-What?
-And now,
let us begin this round,
Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
Following Nam-no,
this man is ready to infect
Chef Ho-young with Poongphobia,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
But this guy is here,
ready to make Yeo-jeong
look more like himself,
Chef Jung Ho-young.
Who's going to give Yeo-jeong
an irresistible appetite?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Begin!
LIVE FEED ON!
-Cooking wine.
-Self-discipline is off the table now.
-Yes. Octopus.
-She's looking to eat good.
Octopus becomes softer with cooking wine.
NEXT, SAUCE FOR THE STIR-FRIED UDON
Adding cooking wine
is a tip to make your octopus tender.
FLOUR, STARCH
And is he making dough?
For udon noodles.
He's making fresh noodles.
Fresh noodles.
-Huh? Emergency.
-It's an emergency.
-Why?
-Emergency.
-It's way too thin.
-It's too thin.
He needs more flour.
Or switch to sujebi.
-Sujebi?
-The batter was too watery.
He must be making fresh noodles.
He's peeling the cucumber.
He's peeling it to make cream.
But the peel has a better color
and a more vibrant smell.
The peel has a stronger smell
It'll smell grassy.
Have you made cucumber cream before?
Something similar,
but it's my first time with actual cream.
Yeo-jeong is slowly becoming suspicious.
"Are you sure you've made this before?"
I was just curious.
"If it's your first time,
you might ruin it."
So cucumber
is the main ingredient for him.
It's also in season in summer.
So I hope many people
watch this and try it at home.
-Butter in water?
-What's he doing?
-In the water?
-The water?
-Is that water or alcohol?
-Water.
Butter in water?
That's a French technique.
-I think he's making the dough.
-You're right.
-The pizza dough.
-Pizza dough.
UDON JUNG MAKES UDON NOODLES
Ho-young makes
fresh udon noodles from scratch.
The dough is still a bit too watery.
It's too watery, right?
That happens with dough
when the first try goes wrong.
-Hey.
-Emergency.
-It's falling apart.
THE EMERGENCY LIGHT IS BUSY TODAY
-It's an emergency.
-Ho-young, you have to do this.
UDON JUNG CAN'T SEEM TO SAVE HIS FACE…
-Switch it.
-Switch it to sujebi.
You should use your hands.
-My hands and feet are cold again.
-Right?
My gosh.
FOR NOW, LET IT REST!
-He's dropping it in there?
-He's adding flour to the pan.
-It's frying powder.
-Frying powder?
Poong's using frying powder?
-Is that for the dough?
-Yes, it's the dough.
That's the pizza dough.
-He just dropped an egg.
-An egg?
It's like choux dough, pate a choux.
-He's making pate a choux?
-It's pate a choux.
-It must be hot.
-Iron Palm training.
Isn't it hot?
I can do this for Princess Yeo-jeong.
For Princess Yeo-jeong…
It's hot!
It must be so hot.
-It's too hot.
-Use a blender.
-Careful.
-That'll turn into scrambled eggs.
Is it okay for the egg to cook?
-It's fine.
-Is it?
-It's okay.
-That's the pizza dough.
Right?
It'll rise when it's deep-fried…
-It rises?
-…without resting, unlike regular dough.
Otherwise, it'll be too hard,
so that's the only way.
-It's a unique way of making dough.
-It looks like a potato.
Can you mix this?
NO IS ON THE MOVE
4. MAKE OCTOPUS SAUCE
BY MIXING SUGAR, SOY SAUCE, AND VINEGAR
LINGERING LOOK
NO STIRS
Ho-young preps seafood.
Seafood. Shrimp and squid.
-I hope the noodles come out well.
-A retry.
-If it's too thin, it won't be good.
-It seems firmer.
-That's not it.
-I hope it works.
-Use your hands.
-It doesn't work!
You have ten minutes left.
It's taking Ho-young
more than five minutes to make dough.
Does he have to redo it?
THROW!
Ho-young looks mad.
LAUGHING
Things aren't going his way.
Good luck, Ho-young.
Keep folding the dough.
You can just make me sujebi.
Yeo-jeong couldn't take it
and said she was fine with sujebi.
I'm really fine.
Do you want some of mine?
Yes, give him yours.
But he wanted to make
udon noodles from scratch.
PRE-MADE SUJEBI
It's working.
It's happening!
RATTLE
IT FEELS A LITTLE LESS WATERY
I should hold the board for him.
-Let me hold it.
-Why won't it…
Jong-won steps in and helps.
He's an honorary firefighter.
It's nice that Jong-won is helping,
but his head is blocking the view
of the noodles coming out.
Jong-won, you have a pretty big head.
THE BIG-HEAD CHEF
We didn't see the noodles in the making.
-The noodles are ready.
-Or your body is too thin.
The udon noodles are ready.
We didn't see them being made
because of Jong-won's head.
His body is just too thin.
The viewers might think
he messed up the dough
and got the noodles from somewhere else.
They won't think that.
We never lie on this show.
What's that? Straight into the pan?
Straight in?
What is that now?
-Cucumber and honey?
-Honey?
-Why?
He cooked the blended cucumber in a pan
and poured honey into it.
-The pizza dough.
-It's the dough.
-Will it cook?
-The whole thing?
It seems way too greasy.
-It's way too oily.
-That's the dough.
It's pate a choux, right?
It's often used to make eclairs and such.
Do you make pizza dough like that too?
-No.
-You don't do that?
-"No"?
-It's not that.
Because I have no time
to add yeast and whatnot.
It reminds me of potato cake.
I think he said
he wanted to turn it into dessert.
He grabs the octopus.
It's out. He cooked it
for exactly seven minutes,
spending half the time cooking that.
Seven minutes.
Seven minutes with cooking wine.
HO-YOUNG USES A CUCUMBER TOO
They're both using cucumbers.
SMASHED CUCUMBER SALAD
TO ACCOMPANY THE OCTOPUS!
CHOPPED INTO BIG PIECES
AND MIXED WITH VINEGAR SAUCE
-The noodles look great.
-The noodles.
-It's getting cooked.
-He actually made it.
It didn't suddenly appear.
6. COOK SQUID, SHRIMP,
ONION, AND GREEN ONION
What's he doing?
What are you doing, Poong?
He's punching the pizza
to keep it from rising.
You do that with pizza dough, right?
You'll pour that on top?
-What?
-You'll pour that?
Wait, that's oil.
-He's pouring oil on top.
-That doesn't look right.
-Wait.
-He's about to deep-fry it.
He made holes in it,
so it will probably cook.
That's really smart of him.
To prevent only the bottom part
being cooked,
he's heating up the top
to cook it thoroughly.
Like an oven.
Instead of flipping it,
he chose to pour oil over it.
LEMON JUICE
IS HE TRULY A GENIUS?
It's rising.
It is? It's rising.
5. SPREAD DOUGH IN A PAN, PUNCH,
THEN POUR HOT OIL ON TOP
-It's literally a high-calorie bomb.
-It looks like jeon.
Six minutes.
Are the noodles ready?
RINSE WELL-COOKED NOODLES IN COLD WATER
INTO THE STIR-FRY!
Stir-fried udon?
The texture will be amazing.
It looks so good.
So he'll do that, then put it in the oven?
-I guess.
-The special soy sauce.
7. FRY SEAFOOD, NOODLES, AND SAUCE
That's Ho-young's expertise.
LOUD ULULATION
ULULATION CONTINUES!
He wants to steal the attention.
-My arm hurts.
-That must be the pizza topping.
You're using those raw?
I'll pickle these.
-You'll pickle them?
-In five minutes?
That's a lot of sugar.
-He's pickling them in sugar.
-In sugar?
-And some salt too. Like pickles.
-Like pickles.
So it'll taste like pickles.
STIR-FRIED UDON, FINISHED!
That looks good.
BUTTER
MOZZARELLA
TOASTED BUCKWHEAT
-Jung-hwan! Please go check.
-Yes?
Go and have a taste.
Ho-young is losing attention.
And pollack roe? That has to be good.
Will he overcome his Poongphobia?
That has to be good.
-He tops it with pollack roe.
-And he'll put that in the oven?
It goes into the oven
with 4 minutes and 30 seconds left.
Four and a half minutes.
The pizza dough. How will this turn out?
Whoa, that's hot. What is this?
You're blending it?
-I have to blend it.
-That cream reminds me
-of when he made the melon fritter.
-The melon.
LIKE THE MELON FRITTER SAUCE?
It's like the melon fritter sauce?
On Poong's side,
it smells like a facial spa.
-I see.
-It reeks of cucumber.
A facial spa?
Yeo-jeong went over to look at the dough.
-I feel anxious about that.
-Jung-hwan, take a look at it.
It's currently rising,
and it's coming apart in the center.
-He should flip that.
-Are you sure you won't flip it?
BLEND AND BOIL!
Take your time. Be careful.
Use one more pan.
Let me use the spatula.
-You can use a dish.
-I can't do that here.
He's about to flip it.
HOW SWEET
WATCH OUT FOR OIL
WONKY
-No!
DO IT AT ONCE!
-Use both hands.
-At once!
SLIPS
-It slipped.
-It failed.
It's his second try.
HE FLIPPED IT!
RELIEVED
ANXIOUS FEET
CLAPPING
-I got it.
-It looks like hotteok. It should be good.
-It's like the crunchy balloon bread.
-I see.
LEMON
ADDING LEMON JUICE TO THE VINEGAR SAUCE
AND THE LONG-AWAITED STEP!
-There's the octopus.
-The octopus.
-It looks tender.
-Yes.
-Jung-hwan.
-After seven minutes. Yes?
Try a piece of the octopus.
Do you have any sauce?
T-t-there. The vinegar…
See how well it's cooked.
-Let me dip it in the sauce.
-Sure.
-What's the octopus like?
-The octopus.
He cooked it for seven minutes.
OCTOPUS♥
Is it cooked perfectly enough
to let him get over Poongphobia?
What's it like?
Is it cooked well?
No, right? Is it still tough?
-Emergency.
-Is it tough?
That can happen with octopus.
He can only escape halfway.
It's a bit tough.
He made cuts right away.
It may be because I had a thick portion.
-It'll be different if it's thin.
-What now?
-Will it turn okay over time?
-I made cuts.
-It's fine.
-He made really thin slices.
-But I had the thick tip.
-At the end,
he made some cuts into it,
so it should be fine.
Mine didn't have cuts.
Starch.
He's using starch?
Wait, he called it a cream,
but he's making it thick with starch.
Jung-hwan, that cucumber cream.
-The cucumber thing.
-What's boiling here?
-Two minutes.
-So this is the topping, right?
-Yes.
-The topping… It looks hot.
I wonder what that's like.
-Cucumber.
-Is it just like a cucumber?
I hope Princess Yeo-jeong likes it.
Does it taste like
something Her Highness would love?
Whoa.
She'd love this!
-It's sweet.
-Really?
It's sweet?
I can't believe it.
The cucumber flavor isn't too strong.
-I see.
-It's there, though.
It must taste like melons.
Yes, it reminds me of melons,
and the texture is like grated potatoes.
It turned out nicely.
One minute.
Octopus with vinegar sauce.
Octopus with vinegar sauce
-and lemon.
-Hurry up.
Lemon zest.
-Under one minute.
-That looks good.
It looks good.
-Poong's dish looks good.
-It does.
-My gosh.
-Hurry up.
Try a little harder, Ho-young.
That looks so good.
He pulled out the udon
with 30 seconds left.
I can see pollack roe and cheese.
The torch.
-Did you use ricotta?
-Not yet.
-What's that?
-Garlic.
-Garlic?
-Garlic in a dessert?
She doesn't really like it.
No, it's okay. I can eat it.
-He's using just the juice.
-A tiny dash.
-Twenty-five seconds.
-Twenty seconds.
He's almost done.
Time to wrap up. Twenty seconds.
-Hurry up.
-Twenty seconds.
-He wrings the cucumber slices.
-Poong… No, Ho-young is done.
-Ho-young finished first.
POONG BEGINS TO PLATE HIS DISH TOO!
It's hot.
Poong, put the toppings on the pizza.
Ten.
-Nine.
-Eight.
-Seven.
-Six.
DROPPING A TON OF CUCUMBER CREAM
AND TOPS IT WITH PICKLES!
-Four.
-Three.
-Two. The end.
-Two. One.
It's over.
-Time's up, Poong.
-All right.
YOU TRIED…
-What about ricotta?
-Where's the cheese?
-Can I put this on top?
-Ask Ho-young.
It's not my call.
-Ask him.
-May I top this just a little?
Just serve it together.
-Right.
-Serve it on the side.
-You're a genius.
-Yes.
-On the side.
-Just serve that.
-It looks kind of classy.
She can top it when she eats it.
-He's so smart.
-Serve it on the side.
KIM POONG FINISHES MAKING
PIZZA NATION, PRINCESS YEO-JEONG
It looks cool too.
-It's a creative presentation.
-Poong is done too.
It's so creative.
DELICIOUSLY PRESENTED
-My gosh.
-Yes.
Everything has been prepared
for Yeo-jeong.
Unlike the first round,
she was a bit more worried,
and she even went closer to look.
Were you quite worried about Poong's dish?
I was surprised
to see the deep-fried dough.
She wasn't sure
if she could actually eat it,
so she had to go see it for herself.
Ho-young finished first,
so please try
Walk Pollack Roely Anywhere You Go.
SWEET AND SOUR OCTOPUS SALAD
& STIR-FRIED UDON
FULL OF POLLACK ROE AND CHEESE
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S
WALK POLLACK ROELY ANYWHERE YOU GO
AMAZED
-It looks so good.
-Ho-young desperately wants a star too.
-That's why he made what he's best at.
-His specialty.
There's cucumber too.
She puts her self-discipline behind.
It looks so good.
Octopus is all about how well it's cooked.
Have a piece of cucumber too.
SO?
It's like an appetizer.
NODDING
So you have to cook it to this level.
-Is it cooked well?
-That's how. Yes.
-It's not tough?
-No.
-It's good.
-She says it's good.
I want to know the recipe. Soy sauce…
It's simple. Two parts soy sauce, one
vinegar, one sugar, and one lemon juice.
What about the red powder?
I sprinkled some red pepper powder.
It's spicy, sour, salty,
-and sweet. Every flavor.
-It has all kinds of flavors.
Because I eat lots of seafood,
I end up getting a bit sick of it.
But this dash of red pepper powder
adds a nice twist.
THAT'S WHY I DID IT
Next, the udon.
Oh, that udon looks so good.
-It looks so good. What do I do?
-I want to try it so bad.
-The Japanese pub style.
-Stir-fried udon.
And baked in the oven, too.
STRETCH
-My gosh.
-Look at how much cheese there is.
I can't say no to that.
Look at that cheese.
A CHEESE BOMB
There's more cheese than I thought.
-It looks so good.
-Yes.
You can probably play
tug-of-war with that.
YOU'RE HILARIOUS
She ate that in one bite.
SLURP
-It must've been forever.
-It looks good.
And the noodles.
The noodles are so good.
Is it? It must've turned out nicely.
FRESH UDON NOODLES ARE PERFECT
We didn't see the noodles being made
because of Jong-won.
You made it, right?
-I did.
-Many viewers are skeptical.
Did Jong-won block the camera
while you swapped out the noodles?
-I think he opened a bag.
-It can't look that good.
You made that? Why does it look so good?
-I'm suspicious.
-I don't know.
-I want a big bite of noodles.
-A big bite of noodles.
She wants a big bite of noodles.
-Great news for Ho-young.
-She's enjoying it.
I want some too.
-She knows how to eat noodles.
-I can't take it anymore.
She controls herself.
She eats like this
only once or twice a year.
-It's so good.
-She loves it,
yet she can't have it too often.
This is so heartbreaking.
It's my first time
trying freshly made udon noodles.
It's the best stir-fried udon of my life.
BEST STIR-FRIED UDON OF HER LIFE
It's so good.
It also has lots of seafood that I love,
so I'm close to forgetting
this guilt over eating flour.
The seafood is great.
-Because it's abundant?
-Yes, and it's good.
-It's so good.
-She looks quite pleased.
And a piece of cucumber, like a side dish.
-It's so good.
-Was it good? Excellent.
-Next.
-Now, the dish in question.
-Poong's cucumber pizza.
-The dessert.
CUCUMBER PIZZA
DEEP-FRIED DOUGH AND SWEET CUCUMBER CREAM
WEBTOON ARTIST KIM POONG'S
PIZZA NATION, PRINCESS YEO-JEONG
He only makes pizza
for those who represent the nation,
and he made one for you.
I just brought extra cream.
-Wait, you can't just bring that here.
-Wait, hear me out.
Why are you adding stuff?
It's the same cucumber cream.
It's the same thing?
If you want more, add some more.
-I don't know how she'd like it, so…
-Yes, sure.
-It was intentional.
-That was why, right?
-It's not that you ran out of time?
-It's not that.
IT'S SAFE(?)
This looks more like cucumber jam.
The dough is different from regular pizza.
It's rather greasy,
so I wonder if that'll be too much.
And…
I'd like lots of cucumber slices.
-Lots of cucumber slices.
-No, this one, with lots of jam too.
I'm getting greedy.
I'm feeling gluttonous.
Lots of cucumber and jam.
-He's serving a piece.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
EVEN THE HOSTS FIND IT FASCINATING
-Try it as is, without anything else.
-Okay.
NOM
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
She carefully took a bite.
SMILING
WHAT DOES HER SMILE MEAN?
She hasn't made a comment yet.
-It must be sweet.
-No comment.
She might swear at him.
INSTEAD, ADDS RICOTTA
"Darn it."
That might be too much.
She should add lots.
A spoonful of ricotta.
If she adds too much,
she won't taste the cucumber.
Her facial expression doesn't look bad.
How will it change with ricotta?
I'll probably look awful.
Does she have to eat it like this?
Must Her Highness eat it like this?
Lock up that man.
-And flog him.
-How dare he do this to Her Highness?
-Yes.
-Lock up Kim Poong.
-Let me try it like this.
-Dip it in the cream.
It felt like cucumber jam when I tried it.
Mmm.
HUH?
This cucumber jam is really good.
I keep calling it jam.
What did you add in here?
Peeled cucumber, then sugar or honey,
and lastly, butter.
That's it. And starch.
And did you boil it?
Yes, I boiled it,
then made it thicker with starch.
-Is she…
-This is odd.
…smiling because it's good?
Or because it's funny?
-We can't tell.
-She either loves it or hates it.
I wouldn't call this pizza.
-It has to be.
-It's more like a rich confectionery.
Confectionery?
The dough is similar to churros dough.
Yes, it's like churros.
But do you know what's odd?
I find myself keep going back for it.
What's with this?
-Do you keep reaching out for it?
-Yes.
Why is that?
It'd be weird if you used your feet.
OH…
-Turn that on.
-That was funny.
Why? It was funny.
-Turn it on.
-She keeps reaching for it.
At my favorite pizza joint,
they have dessert pizzas
-made with blueberries and cream cheese.
-Or chocolate.
It's like another dessert pizza
that's on the menu.
That was what I intended.
Please try Chef Ho-young's dish first.
-Did he chop the pollack roe?
-It's because she loves noodles.
NODDING
There's a bit of smoky flavor
on the pollack roe.
And that helps me keep eating
without getting sick of it.
I finished it.
And I wasn't even hungry.
You ate the rest all alone?
I thought the noodles would fail,
but the finished product
looks even and nice
like store-bought noodles.
I couldn't quite see it.
Did you cut the noodles
after you flattened it?
The same machine cuts the noodles too.
Even Yeo-jeong is suspicious.
-They may have switched it out.
-No, wait.
When did he chop the noodles
after flattening the dough?
I really didn't see it.
ARE YOU WATCHING THIS ON TV, YEO-JEONG?
We should've seen it,
but Jong-won's head blocked it.
INNOCENT
Next, Poong's dish.
-This is odd.
-How will you feel about it?
Be honest.
Let's share our opinions honestly.
WHAT'S IT LIKE, EVERYONE?
It's either love it or hate it.
I see why he used garlic.
INHALES
At the end…
2 HITS
3 HITS
UNSURE?
This has a cute flavor to it.
-I see.
-Isn't it intriguing?
This would be a great dish to feed kids
who don't like cucumbers.
It's not too complicated.
There's no need to analyze this.
Also, that slight dash of garlic
works very well with me. That single dash.
There's a confectionery snack called
French Pie.
-That's it. French Pie.
-It felt like I was eating that.
It brought back great memories,
and crunchy cucumber added a good texture.
-Like French Pie.
-The ones with apple flavor and such.
This pizza reminds me of my childhood.
My grandma had a perilla leaf farm.
-What?
-Back to the farm?
And the neighboring granny
had a cucumber farm.
I fell asleep there
while playing hide-and-seek,
then woke up in the Mediterranean.
A JOURNEY TO THE MEDITERRANEAN
FROM HIS GRANDMA'S NEIGHBOR'S FARM
The mixture of cucumber and ricotta
is a very Mediterranean way of eating.
We should call this Greek pizza.
Actual Greeks will be mad
when they see this.
That was an excellent comparison.
Thank you.
It's very delicious.
And this familiar balance
isn't so bad either.
But if he wanted to add
a little more impact,
he could've salted the dough.
Then it would've been perfect.
You should've told him.
I had no idea what he was up to.
Exactly. He thought he'd manage.
-The biggest eater, Nam-no.
-Nam-no.
-Time to earn your keep.
-This isn't a buffet.
Why do we always give him
multiple servings?
What's that salt doing here?
I tried it with salt as he suggested.
After a bit of salt on the cucumber pizza,
the flavor became brighter.
You tried it right away?
ALWAYS QUICK TO ACT WHEN IT COMES TO FOOD
-It's like Greek salad. Feta and cucumber.
-Greek salad?
But it had been made by a Chinese man.
-It has that Chinese bread flavor.
-It does.
It's like the thin wheat crêpes.
A Chinese man residing in Greece?
-A Chinese man in Greece?
POONG MAKES IT HAPPEN
-It's time to choose.
-Yes.
The choice is Yeo-jeong's.
Press one for Ho-young
and two for Poong.
Make your decision and press one button!
-I did.
-You did?
She makes it so quick.
She makes a quick decision
with a smile on her face.
Ho-young looks rather anxious.
-He's in a losing streak.
-Four losses against Poong.
Let's see the result.
-Show us.
-Yeo-jeong's choice.
Self-Discipline Was Just the Beginning.
Will Poong prove himself again
to be strong against Ho-young?
Or will Ho-young get his revenge?
Who did she choose?
Who's the winner?
Yeo-jeong's choice!
JUNG HO-YOUNG WINS
Jung Ho-young.
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S
WALK POLLACK ROELY ANYWHERE YOU GO WINS
Ho-young breaks his losing streak.
He got his revenge on Poong.
When people eat something fatty,
they joke, "The food is fatty, not me."
And I don't like doing that
because it sounds like an excuse.
But when I had this,
it made me want to go,
"Whatever. I didn't eat any noodles."
It felt like that.
-You only had seafood.
-Yes, like, "I only had seafood."
I wanted to do that from time to time.
I feel small and lose my confidence
whenever I lose to Poong,
as opposed to other chefs.
-Yes, seriously.
-So through this victory,
I got to recover a bit of confidence.
-Thank you so much.
-Right?
You can walk back home triumphantly today.
Please put a star on Chef Ho-young.
It's his seventh star, seventh win!
-It was delicious.
-Ho-young!
He can now walk confidently.
Congratulations!
Ho-young's seventh win!
An engineering major
and an intellectual heartthrob.
We probably studied
a few similar subjects.
I also attended a vo-tech school.
PRESENTING
THE INTELLECTUAL HEARTTHROB'S FRIDGE!
The ones that arrive early go to the back.
First-in, first-out.
I'm in a state of hyperarousal…
HIS ENGINEER BRAIN
I hear you talk to yourself often.
I find myself mumbling.
"What's in the fridge?"
"The traffic is heavy."
THE OLD ENGINEERING MAJOR DUDE(?)
ASKS FOR A SOUP DISH ROUND
THE KIND OF SOUP HE'LL LOVE
RED RED
IT LOOKS SO GOOD
Old man, come and hold this.
THE OLD DUDE IS HERE
APPLAUDING AT THE OLD GUY
THE OLD DUDE NEVER DIES…
AMAZED!
MAN!
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL
A ROUND BETWEEN TWO ITALIAN CHEFS
AN EMERGENCY ALREADY?
Who turned off the oven?
-Maybe Chef Canine.
-I think he's possessed by evil.
He asked me for the circuit box.
No. Yes.
He asked me too.
"Do you think I can
cut the wire with my canine?"
Do you see this, Jee Seok-jin?
MISTAKE OVER THE LINE
Jee Seok-jin isn't here!
CAN HE SAVE HIMSELF FROM THE MISTAKE?
Does your husband
look similar to Seok-jin?
He said he looked like Jee Seok-jin.
-Jee Seok-jin?
Subtitle translation by:
Eunsook Youn